so how's our bearing looking all good it's perfect just like you nami swan
i've just about got these holes patched we'd be in a whole world of worry if i hadn't had the
foresight to grab all this scrap lumber back at the dock you're the best usop this should hold her
together for a while it's out fuel burned out huh hey who's up we're going down we got a moving
chopper hurry up and grab those boards just hang in there octopus balloon get down moron
that was way too close
that should help get rid of the stinging that's two times now you've helped us out of a real tight spot
thanks buddy thank you again for all your help i hope you make lots of new friends out in the blue sea
stay strong and don't take any crap from those grand line octopi you travel safe sushi platter
careful out there thanks for everything
now then set the sails top two let's find the next island whoa hey come on loopy can't we rest for
a little while you're a little too relaxed listen that attitude isn't going to get us very far on
these seas i don't think i want to hear this the waves look a little too strange for comfort so it's back to
work turn to port anything for you nami dear
this doesn't look good for us there's something in the wave is that the breeze
what's all the ruckus out here
meekwee
quit pushing come on stop it let me go why are they fighting
philomys sarkis isn't someone gonna stop them
No more! I'm begging you! Why are you making me do this?
What the hell is going on?
I've never seen Sarkis bleed like that.
Why, you ask? Why am I making you?
Sarkis. Bellamy.
I'm making you do this because you've made a mockery of this symbol.
Does the Sky Island exist or not?
Is the legendary City of Gold real or not?
The truth doesn't really matter, now does it?
You play the opposing sides off each other to twist them to your will.
That's what I told you. Right, Bellamy?
I think that's Don Quixote Don Flamingo.
He's one of the seven warlords of the sea!
I heard his bounty's over 300 million. What's a guy like him doing here?
You've really let me down, and I've got zero tolerance for useless punks like you.
No, not again! My body's moving!
It's on its own! I can't control it!
Please!
No!
Bellamy!
Just give me one more chance to set things right.
I swear we'll loyally follow your every command.
Bellamy!
Let it go, Bellamy!
I might have lost, but I've never once acted against your principles!
I swear on your symbol! Please!
I had reasons for my actions!
I couldn't just let the Straw Hats get away!
They were bound to find you someday if I didn't stop them!
Oh, what a touching sentiment. Such genuine loyalty.
Your concern for my well-being is duly noted, Bellamy.
There's a new era quickly approaching, so your actions here won't really matter.
But, I still have no use for you.
Don't love it!
He wiped out Bellamy as easily as stomping on a baby!
He was worth 55 million!
The beginning is upon us.
I suggest you prepare.
We're drawing close to a new world in which only true pirates can survive.
The weak should run while they still can,
or be swept away by the tides of time!
as they roll back to reveal a new era of champions!
AHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!
Seems pretty calm now.
It's too soon to lower our guard.
Emergency alert!
Unknown ship spotted at 12 o'clock!
Are they bad guys?
They picked a bad time.
Well, they don't have a single flag or sail up.
I don't know what kind of ship it is.
It's naked?
Who would do that to their ship?
What are they doing out here without sail?
How should I know?
What's even weirder,
the crew is way too small for a ship that size.
Also,
they look like they're catatonic or something.
They're just sitting around in a daze.
The sea monkeys!
Again?
They must have followed us!
Aw, crap!
There's no wind!
Hurry and furl the sail!
Come on, start rowing!
What's wrong with them?
They're headed towards the sea monkeys!
That wave's gonna swallow them whole!
Hey!
Wake up!
There's a giant wave filled with sea monkeys!
Turn around!
Huh?
A ship?
Whoa!
It's a pirate ship!
Come on, man!
On your feet!
We gotta raid that ship and swipe it out!
Oh, no!
You're going to see them all of us!
We're gonna reach out to our ship!
All of us!
Ah, crap, there's no wind!
Hurry and furl the sail!
Come on, start rowing!
What's wrong with them?
They're heading towards the sea monkeys!
That wave's gonna swallow them whole!
Hey, wake up!
There's a giant wave filled with sea monkeys!
Turn around!
Huh?
A ship, whoa...
It's a pirate ship!
that ship and swipe their treasure.
Wait, we're gonna get crushed by that giant wing!
Yeah, but we can't let them get away.
Ready to the cannons!
You ain't the boss, why don't you two?
Turn, somebody turn!
Wow, that's gotta be the worst crew ever.
Forget about those idiots.
They only wanna steal our treasure.
Which way do we turn?
Who knows?
Where's the navigator?
Give orders!
What navigator?
Captain!
What captain?
What the?
Who fired the cannon?
It's too late, we're going down!
You're a bunch of worthless morons!
No, you're a bunch of morons!
What a stupid way for...
Man, it's just one terrible thing after another these days.
At least it's calm.
Those gargantuan waves earlier were actually caused by the sea monkeys.
The humidity and temperature seem like they're pretty stable now.
So we've gotta be in the next island's climate zone.
Ugh, you hear that, Robin?
Any islands?
We've been approaching one for a while now.
Why didn't you tell us?
You are way too secretive.
Look, maybe tell us next time you see an island.
You know, like this!
Land ahoy!
Land!
I see land!
Yeah, yeah!
Now you see it!
The fog looks pretty thick.
Don't ignore me!
Heavy fog?
That's not good.
Hey, Chopper!
I need you to stand forward watch!
Right!
Robin, do you have any idea how long we've been waiting to see another island?
Sorry, won't happen again.
As long as you mean it!
Okay.
You know, I can't stop thinking about that ship.
They didn't have a captain or a navigator or even sails!
It was like they had no idea what they were doing!
Now what kind of self-respecting pirates would head out to sea like that?
I'm guessing they got in a battle and lost.
Captain probably got killed and then their ship got plundered.
But that can't be it!
I gotta look at their ship!
It was in perfect condition.
No signs of battle.
But it was still completely stripped clean of anything a pirate would need to survive!
They probably weren't even pirates then.
Forget it.
They look like pirates to me.
Crummy pirates, but still.
I don't know.
I've got a bad feeling about this somehow.
Have you ever had a good one?
Anyway, I wonder if there's a town!
I hope they got a shipyard!
Rufy, don't jump off right away!
I hope we can find a knowledgeable shipwright to join us.
Get the anchor ready!
We're near the shore!
That feeling just got worse.
Hey Chopper, Usopp's come down with another bout of scaredy-cat-itis.
Well, there's no care for that.
All right, let's go, let's go!
You're kidding.
There's nothing at all!
It's like a blank slate!
Cool!
All I can see is grass and trees!
Man, this place is kind of depressing.
I wonder if anyone actually lives here.
Jeez, it's like they have no concept of unknown danger.
You can see clear across the island and there's no threat in sight.
You see something, Chopper?
Huh?
Human?
Have you ever seen a human this furry and enormous?
It's got to be some kind of bear!
Whoa, it's so long!
It's a long bear!
I'm getting dizzy up here!
Hey, check out how long this apple is!
Whoa!
I'm just realizing it, but the trees are long too!
Hey, look!
Is that a house over there?
Yeah, I guess it kind of looks like a house.
Let's go check it out.
Let's go check it out!
Are you guys related?
That's a deer!
I'm a reindeer!
Shake!
Hey, Chopper!
Watch this!
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Don't play, dude!
Stop!
Now beg!
It's miles long!
Wow!
I can't even see its head!
Where the hell'd they run off to?
They were right there just a minute ago.
We might as well disembark.
There's got to be food on this island.
Hey, Earth to Robin!
We're going to jump ship, okay?
Right.
Everything on this island is so long!
How did it get this way?
Maybe it's the gravity?
Oh, my body feels so stretched out just from thinking about it!
What is a point in a place like this?
Hello?
Anyone home?
What do you think you're doing?
You can't go in there!
For all we know, the boss of the island lives in this house, and he's probably some terrifyingly
long man-snake monster that'll swallow us whole!
Oh, it's empty.
No one's home.
Huh?
Hey, Luffy!
Usopp!
There's a giraffe out here!
Really?
Eee!
Gah!
Chomper, that's not a giraffe!
That's a horse with a long neck!
A long horse!
You're a horse?
Eee!
Wow, what a pretty horse!
She said thank you, and her name's Shelly!
Going by the saddle she's got on her, her owner must be close by.
Huh?
Hey, what are you looking at?
Over there.
There's something up with those two bamboo trees.
Huh?
Yeah, you're right!
Talk about tall!
I can't even see the top!
That's not it.
Look closer.
Huh?
Uh...
Gah!
They're moving!
They must be part of some long animal!
That thing's attacking Luffy!
Are you okay?
Get back here, bamboo!
Be careful, Luffy!
Bum, bum!
All right!
You did it!
Yeah!
I beat it!
Why are you alone?
Where's your owner?
You don't know where?
That sounds awfully lonely.
It might be bad guys!
Stay there!
And hide!
What's going on?
Well, uh...
I think that bamboo tree was possessed by this spirit.
Hey, what's the deal?
They blocked in our ship.
This can't be good.
That's the ship I saw earlier.
You looking for a fight?
Because we'll be happy to give you one.
We are the notorious Foxy Pirates!
We want more than just a fight from you!
We want a showdown!
A spirit?
Well, yeah.
What else pops out of a tree?
Hey, can you speak?
You're acting like I don't remember you.
Of course I do.
What have you been up to all these years?
Huh?
You guys know him?
Never seen him.
Same here.
Ah, well, that would explain why I don't remember you then.
Who are you, old man?
And tell us the truth!
If you want my name, it's Tonjit.
But what I intend to give you is my gratitude.
I've been hoping someone would knock me down off those stilts.
Off what?
Uh...
Oh, they are stilts.
We didn't realize because they were so long.
We couldn't even see you.
I'm not surprised.
I couldn't even see the ground up there.
So then, just to get this straight, you're not a bamboo tree spirit.
You're just an old guy whose stilts I happen to think were attacking me.
What were you doing walking around on those stilts anyway?
Well, I've always been a stilt enthusiast, so I decided to break some records and make the world's longest stilts by using the bamboo on this island.
I managed to get on them with a little effort, but then I was too scared to climb down.
That's just plain crazy.
I was up there 10 years.
Really crazy!
Wait, you were up on those stilts for 10 whole years?!
That's right, and to make matters worse, the bamboo kept growing the entire time.
It just kept getting harder and harder to climb down.
So terrifying.
How did you live up there for 10 years?!
Well, most of the trees on this island are just as tall as my stilts, if not taller, so I was well fed from their fruit.
He talks about it like it's no big deal.
10 long years of his life.
And speaking of stuff that's long, how come every living creature on this island is so insanely long?
It might seem crazy to an outsider, but there is a reason.
As I'm sure you've noticed, the island is nothing but grass and trees.
It's dull, so everything grew long out of a longing for excitement.
He can't be serious.
You see that over there?
Platypus.
Ah, you just said it longer!
That one is a dachshund dog.
Whoa, is that the same dog?
It's still passing?
Oh, man!
And there are dangerous animals as well.
See?
Over there is a snow leopard.
I'd steer clear of it.
Why is its head the only thing that's long?!
HBR-
Hmmmm...
A bl-via-via-via...
I'm the captain.
Get out, Luffy! Don't just agree like that!
On the next, One Piece, a Davey back with the Foxy Pirates.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!